Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5, Section 2: Boxes 23-44 1870-2017
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
- U.S. Internal Revenue Service, Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Item 22: A Guidebook: How to Introduce Egronomics in IRS Automotion Projects, Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
    By U.S. Internal Revenue Service. March 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Rules of Conduct, Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
    By U.S. Internal Revenue Service. Informational Booklet - July 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: A Health Improvement Program, Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
    By U.S. Internal Revenue Service. March 1, 1985. Item is in English.
- U.S. National Administrative Office, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: List of Documents from the Department of Labor that are available to the Public, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
    By U.S. National Administrative Office. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: NAFTA's Brojen Promises: Job Creation Under NAFTA, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
    By Peter Cooper and Lori Wallach. September 1995. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Correcting the Record, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
    By U.S. National Administrative Office. September 2, 1993. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Underground Economy of the United States, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
    By U.S. National Administrative Office. Occasional Paper No. 2 - September 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The North American Agreement on Labor Cooperation: An Assessment of its First Year's Implementation, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Summary of the Understanding on Emergency Action, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
    By U.S. National Administrative Office. Article. Item is in English.
- United States. National Committee of The Int'l. Cargo Handling Coordination Association, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: ICHCA-USA, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
    By U.S. National Committee of the International Cargo Handling Coordination Association. News Release - October 15, 1981. Item is in English.
- National Labor Board, United States, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Statement of E. T. Weir to the National Labor Board, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
    By National Labor Board of the United States. October 16, 1933. Item is in English.
- National Labor Relations Board, United States, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: "The Record Speaks", Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
    By Elinore Herrick. Item is in English.
- U.S. Office of Personnel Management, Publication (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Federal Manager's Guide to Washington, Publication (Box 31, Folder 11)
    By National Labor Relations Board. Book - December 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Federal Negotiated Grievance Procedures, Publication (Box 31, Folder 11)
    By U.S. Office of Personnel Management. January 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Taking Action on the Problem Employee, Publication (Box 31, Folder 11)
    By U.S. Office of Personnel Management. Informational Pamphlet - March 1983. Item is in English.
- U.S. Railroad Board - Retirement manuals, handbooks, Publication (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Milwaukee Railroad Restucturing Act, Publication (Box 31, Folder 12)
    By U.S. Railroad Retirement Board. January 1980. Item is in English.
- U.S. Railway Labor Board, Publication (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Increase in Cost of Living and Prices, 1914 to 1920, Publication (Box 31, Folder 13)
    By W. Jett Lauck. Pamphlet. Item is in English.
- US Steel, Publication (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Are you one of the leaders we need?, Publication (Box 31, Folder 14)
    By United States Steel. September 1979. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: US Steel News, Publication (Box 31, Folder 14)
    By United States Steel. Magazine. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: US Steel News, Publication (Box 31, Folder 14)
    By United States Steel. 81/4. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: US Steel News, Publication (Box 31, Folder 14)
    By United States Steel. 81/2. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: United States Steel and the Environment, Publication (Box 31, Folder 14)
    By United States Steel. Informational Booklet. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: US Steel News, Publication (Box 31, Folder 14)
    By United States Steel. July 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: US Steel News, Publication (Box 31, Folder 14)
    By United States Steel. 82/4. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: US Steel News, Publication (Box 31, Folder 14)
    By United States Steel. 83/2. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: US Steel News, Publication (Box 31, Folder 14)
    By United States Steel. 83/3. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: US Steel News, Publication (Box 31, Folder 14)
    By United States Steel. 84/1. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Continuing Your Education, Publication (Box 31, Folder 14)
    By United States Steel. August 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Application for Employment, Publication (Box 31, Folder 14)
    By United States Steel. May 1978 - Form. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Sign - Up and Verification Form, Publication (Box 31, Folder 14)
    By United States Steel. Form. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Policy Number 0002, 6002 and 6003, Publication (Box 31, Folder 14)
    By United States Steel. July 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: You and the NEW United States Steel Corporation, Publication (Box 31, Folder 14)
    By United States Steel. Folder cointaing Information. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Summary Plan Description of United States Steel 1984 Salaried Pension Rules, Publication (Box 31, Folder 14)
    By United States Steel. Amended January 1, 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: United States Steel 1984 Salaried Pension Rules, Publication (Box 31, Folder 14)
    By United States Steel. January 1, 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Supplement to Summary Plan Description of United States Steel Corporation, Publication (Box 31, Folder 14)
    By United States Steel. Savings Fund Plan for Salaried Employees - November 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Flexible Benefits Plan, Publication (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Item 20: Program of Insurance Benefits - Life and Disability Benefits, Publication (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Item 21: Group Insurance Plan Life and Disability Benefits, Publication (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Item 22: Things You Need To KnowDecisions You Need To Make As A New Employee of United States Steel, Publication (Box 31, Folder 14)
    By United States Steel. January, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Things You Need To KnowDecisions You Need To Make As A New Management Employee of United States Steeel, Publication (Box 31, Folder 14)
    By United States Steel. January 1, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Affimative Action Equal Employment Opportunity Program, Publication (Box 31, Folder 14)
    By United States Steel. August 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: US Steel News, Publication (Box 31, Folder 14)
    By United States Steel. 85/6. Item is in English.
- US Steel - Organs, Publication (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: US Steel News, Publication (Box 31, Folder 15)
    By United States Steel. 84/3. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: US Steel News, Publication (Box 31, Folder 15)
    By United States Steel. 84/2. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: US Steel News, Publication (Box 31, Folder 15)
    By United States Steel. 84/4. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: US Steel News, Publication (Box 31, Folder 15)
    By United States Steel. 85/1. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: US Steel News, Publication (Box 31, Folder 15)
    By United States Steel. 85/2. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: US Steel News, Publication (Box 31, Folder 15)
    By United States Steel. 85/3. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: US Steel News, Publication (Box 31, Folder 15)
    By United States Steel. 85/4. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: US Steel News, Publication (Box 31, Folder 15)
    By United States Steel. 85/5. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: US Steel News, Publication (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Item 10: US Steel News, Publication (Box 31, Folder 15)
    By United States Steel. 86/1. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: US Steel News, Publication (Box 31, Folder 15)
    By United States Steel. 86/2. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: US Steel News, Publication (Box 31, Folder 15)
    By United States Steel. 83/1. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: US Steel News, Publication (Box 31, Folder 15)
    By United States Steel. 81/3. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: US Steel News, Publication (Box 31, Folder 15)
    By United States Steel. 1/81. Item is in English.
- US Treasury Dept., Publication (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: ECSP: Employee Counseling Services Program, Publication (Box 31, Folder 16)
    By U.S. Treasury Department. Informational Pamphlet. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Opportunties at Treasury, Publication (Box 31, Folder 16)
    By U.S. Treasury Department. Folder with Information. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Management Handbook, Publication (Box 31, Folder 16)
    By U.S. Treasury Department. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Fire and Chemical Emergency Contingency Manual, Publication (Box 31, Folder 16)
    By U.S. Treasury Department. July 3, 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Production of Government Securities, Publication (Box 31, Folder 16)
    By U.S. Treasury Department. September 1980 - Pamphlet. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Fire and Chemical Emergency Contingency Handbook, Publication (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Item 7: Federal Employees Retirement System, Publication (Box 31, Folder 16)
    By U.S. Treasury Department. September 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: 1987 Enrollment Information Guide and Plan Comparison Chart, Publication (Box 31, Folder 16)
    By U.S. Treasury Department. November 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Memornadum - Alternative Work Schedules - Non-bargaining Unit Employees, Publication (Box 31, Folder 16)
    By U.S. Treasury Department. January 10, 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Memorandum - Manager's Handbook, Publication (Box 31, Folder 16)
    By U.S. Treasury Department. July 25, 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Executive Summary - General Performace Appraisal System, Publication (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Item 12: Part VII - Personnel Administration, Publication (Box 31, Folder 16)
    By U.S. Treasury Department. March 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Occupational Safety & Health Manual, Publication (Box 31, Folder 16)
    By U.S. Treasury Department. March 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: How to file and EEO, Publication (Box 31, Folder 16)
    By U.S. Treasury Department. Pamphlet. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Physical Security Responsibilities, Publication (Box 31, Folder 16)
    By U.S. Treasury Department. Pamphlet - June 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Orientation, Publication (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Item 17: Flexitime In - The Bureau of the Public Debt - Employee Handbook, Publication (Box 31, Folder 16)
    By U.S. Treasury Department. August 15, 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Performace Plan and Appraisal Form for Non-SES, Non Merit Pay Employees, Publication (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Item 19: Employee Counseling Service Program Flyer, Publication (Box 31, Folder 16)
    By U.S. Treasury Department. December, 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: PD News, Publication (Box 31, Folder 16)
    By U.S. Treasury Department. December 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Opportunities at Treasury, Publication (Box 31, Folder 16)
- U.S. Treasury Dept. "Supervisory handbook for Labor and Employee Rel", Publication (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Financial Management Service - Supervisory Handbook for Labor and Employee Relations, Publication (Box 31, Folder 17)
    By U.S. Department of the Treasury. Item is in English.
- U.S. Wage Stabilization Board, Publication (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: The Economics of the Guaranteed Wage, Publication (Box 31, Folder 18)
    By Emerson P. Schmidt. February 13, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Statement with Regard to the Unemployment Benefits Demand, Publication (Box 31, Folder 18)
    By U.S. Wage Stabilization Board. Item is in English.
- University of Minnesota - Industrial Relations Center, Publication (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Public Policy and Emergency Disputes, Publication (Box 31, Folder 19)
    By C. F. Smythe. Booklet. Item is in English.
- UPJOHN - Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Volume 32, Number 2 - March-April, 1994. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol. 26, Nos. 1 &, January-February 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vo. 18, No.4, April 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol. 18, Nos. 1 & 2, january-February 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol. 18, No. 3, March 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol. 18, Nos. 7 & 8, July-August 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol. 18, No. 9, September 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol. 18, No. 10, October 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. November 1980 - Awards Special. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol. 18, No. 11, November 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.19, Nos. 1 & 2, January-February 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.19, No. 3, March 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol. 19, No. 4, April 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.19, No.6, June 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol. 19, Nos. 7 & 8, July/August 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol. 19, No. 11, November 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol. 20, Nos. 1 & 2, January-February 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. November 1981 - Awards Special. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol. 19, No. 9, September 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.19, No. 12, December 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol. 20, No. 12, December 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol. 20, No. 4, April 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol. 20, No. 6, June 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol. 20, Nos. 7 & 8, July-August 1982. Item is in English.
- UPJOHN - Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol. 20, No. 9, September 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol. 20, No. 10, October 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.20, No. 11, November 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.19, No. 10, October 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol. 21, Nos. 1 & 2, January-February 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.21, No. 5, May 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.21,No. 3, March 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol. 21, No.5, June 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol. 21, Nos. 7 & 8, July-August 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.21,No.9, September 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol. 21,No.4, April 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol. 21, No. 10, October 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.22, No.3, March 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.21,No.11, November 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.21,No.12, December 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.20,No.3, March 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.22,No.4, April 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.22,No.6, June 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.22, Nos. 7 & 8, July-August 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.22,No.9, September 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.22,No.10, October 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.22,No.11, November 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.22,No.12, December 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.23,Nos. 1 & 2, January-February 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.23,No.5, May 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.23,Nos. 7 & 8, July-August 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. January 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.23,No.4,April 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.23,No.3, March 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.23, No.6, June 1985. Item is in English.
- UPJOHN - Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.26, No.9, September 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.26, No. 10, October 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.26,No.19,December 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.26, No.11, November 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.27, No. 1 & 2, January-February 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.27, No.3, March 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.23, No.9, September 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.23, No.10, October 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.23,Nos. 11 & 12, November-December 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.24,No.3, March 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.24,Nos. 1 & 2, January-February 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.24,No.4, April 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.24, No.5, May 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.24,No.6, June 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.24, Nos. 7 & 8, July-August 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.24,No.9, September 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.24,No.10, October 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.24, Nos. 11 & 12, November-December 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.25,Nos. 1 & 2, January-February 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.25, No.3, March 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.25,No.4, April 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.25,No.5, May 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.25,Nos. 7 & 8, July-August 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.25,No.6, June 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.25,No.10, October 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.25,No.11, November 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.25,No.12, December 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.26,No.4, April 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.26,No.5, May 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.26,No.6, June 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.26,Nos. 7 & 8, July-August 1988. Item is in English.
- UPJOHN - Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 4)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vo.27, Nos. 7 & 8, July-August 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Intercom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 4)
    By UPJOHN INTERCOM. Vol.27, No.4, April 1989. Item is in English.